<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quotes>
  <name>
    <number>1</number>
    <quote>One day you will wake up and there won't be any more time to do the things you've always wanted. Do it now</quote>
    <author>Paulo Coelho</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>2</number>
    <quote>As we express our gratitude, we must never forget that the highest appreciation is not to utter words, but to live by them.</quote>
    <author>John F. Kennedy</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>3</number>
    <quote>Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going.</quote>
    <author>Jim Ryun</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>4</number>
    <quote>The secret of getting ahead is getting started.</quote>
    <author>Mark Twain</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>5</number>
    <quote>Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.</quote>
    <author>Mark Twain</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>6</number>
    <quote>Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.</quote>
    <author>Mark Twain</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>7</number>
    <quote>It always seems impossible until it's done.</quote>
    <author>Nelson Mandela</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>8</number>
    <quote>With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts.</quote>
    <author>Eleanor Roosevelt</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>9</number>
    <quote>Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it.</quote>
    <author>Charles R. Swindoll</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>10</number>
    <quote>My mission in life is not merely to survive, but to thrive; and to do so with some passion, some compassion, some humor, and some style.</quote>
    <author>Maya Angelou</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>11</number>
    <quote>Good friends, good books and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life.</quote>
    <author>Mark Twain</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>12</number>
    <quote>Don't let schooling interfere with your education.</quote>
    <author>Mark Twain</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>13</number>
    <quote>No matter what happens in life, be good to people. Being good to people is a wonderful legacy to leave behind.</quote>
    <author>Taylor Swift</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>14</number>
    <quote>Tact is the art of making a point without making an enemy.</quote>
    <author>Isaac Newton</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>15</number>
    <quote>To be able to look back upon ones life in satisfaction, is to live twice.</quote>
    <author>Khalil Gibran</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>16</number>
    <quote>A little knowledge that acts is worth infinitely more than much knowledge that is idle.</quote>
    <author>Khalil Gibran</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>17</number>
    <quote>If you can dream it, you can do it.</quote>
    <author>Walt Disney</author>
  </name>
    <name>
    <number>18</number>
    <quote>The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing.</quote>
    <author>Walt Disney</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>19</number>
    <quote>Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be strengthened, ambition inspired, and success achieved.</quote>
    <author>Helen Keller</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>20</number>
    <quote>Be sure you put your feet in the right place, then stand firm.</quote>
    <author>Abraham Lincoln</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>21</number>
    <quote>Girl power is about loving yourself and having confidence and strength from within, so even if you're not wearing a sexy outfit, you feel sexy.</quote>
    <author>Nicole Scherzinger</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>22</number>
    <quote>You can either see yourself as a wave in the ocean or you can see yourself as the ocean.</quote>
    <author>Oprah Winfrey</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>23</number>
    <quote>We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be.</quote>
    <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>24</number>
    <quote>I want to stand as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't see from the center.</quote>
    <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>25</number>
    <quote>We have to continually be jumping off cliffs and developing our wings on the way down.</quote>
    <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>26</number>
    <quote>And I asked myself about the present: how wide it was, how deep it was, how much was mine to keep</quote>
    <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
  </name>
  <name>
    <number>27</number>
    <quote>I tell you, we are here on Earth to fart around, and don't let anybody tell you different.</quote>
    <author>Kurt Vonnegut</author>
  </name>
</quotes>
